<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>crazy-ass-broad</title>
    <link href="http://crazyassbroad.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="http://crazyassbroad.com" />
    <updated>2018-01-02T23:34:19-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Jenn</name>
    </author>
    <id>http://crazyassbroad.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Second Day of The New Years Resolution</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jenn</name>
        </author>
        <link href="http://crazyassbroad.com/second-day-of-the-new-years-resolution.html"/>
        <id>http://crazyassbroad.com/second-day-of-the-new-years-resolution.html</id>

        <updated>2018-01-02T23:33:53-05:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="http://crazyassbroad.com/media/posts/7/pic12.jpg" alt="" />
                
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The feel of today was weird. Nothing too out of the ordinary. Feeling uneasy. Maybe due to the storm but the pit of my stomach is feeling icky... </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">I had prewrote a post yesterday for today. &nbsp;For those who know me have heard this conversation before... or you've had this conversation with me.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you are going to remember one thing, everyone is the star of their own movie. &nbsp;You're just a guest appearance in their&nbsp;story. If you look at that in the sense that everyone is a little self involved and that sometimes their reactions to something is reflection on their previous scenes you'll be alright interacting with those around you. I am trying to remember that I calm down my own inner dialog.</span></p>
<p>Advice I am trying to give myself... Take everyday with a grain of salt. Try to think of one thing a day that makes you feel grateful and can make me smile. The more you can smile, the better your outlook on life, and the better your life will be.&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mood: Feeling Anxious... Not sure why but feeling like something is about to happen. Hopefully, it's not too bad. Maybe it's weather related...&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Weather: COLD!!!&nbsp;High 18/Low this morning -13</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Goal for the Day: &nbsp;Help someone. Make someone smile.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>Quote of the Day:&nbsp;</p>
<p><img src="http://crazyassbroad.com/media/posts/7/goal-2.jpg" alt="" width="310" height="163"></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Happy National Hangover Day!!! </title>
        <author>
            <name>Jenn</name>
        </author>
        <link href="http://crazyassbroad.com/happy-national-hangover-day.html"/>
        <id>http://crazyassbroad.com/happy-national-hangover-day.html</id>

        <updated>2018-01-01T20:23:12-05:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="http://crazyassbroad.com/media/posts/6/hungover.jpg" alt="" />
                <p><img src="http://crazyassbroad.com/media/posts/6/hungover.jpg" alt="" width="398" height="398"></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">January 1st, National Hangover Day. It was just that.. After a full day of recovery, I decided to venture out into the frigid winter cold. So I drove, with my hands frozen to the steering wheel to the local grocery.&nbsp;</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Everyone was dressed like me; wearing sweats, giant coats, and NO MAKEUP! We all looked like we had too much fun the night before and were just looking for the cure for 2017, haha.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mood: Sleepy but hopeful was my first post... until the page froze and I lost everything I had written. So now a little pissed, dehydrated, and a little bit hopeful!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Weather: COLD!!! High of 12, Low of -1.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Goal for the Day: Sleep more, eat&nbsp;good food, and prepare for the work week.</span></p>
<p>Quote of the Day:&nbsp;</p>
<p><img src="http://crazyassbroad.com/media/posts/6/goal-point-o.jpg" alt="" width="420" height="294"></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>New Year, New You?</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jenn</name>
        </author>
        <link href="http://crazyassbroad.com/new-year-new-you.html"/>
        <id>http://crazyassbroad.com/new-year-new-you.html</id>

        <updated>2018-01-01T20:22:59-05:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="http://crazyassbroad.com/media/posts/5/newyears.jpg" alt="" />
                <p><img class="align-center" src="http://crazyassbroad.com/media/posts/5/newyears.jpg" alt="" width="364" height="364"></p>

<p>It seems like Americans, on social media, are more&nbsp;pessimistic than usual this year. "New Year, New You...YEAH RIGHT!" More than worrying about something to resolve, we should really try to adjust our attitude towards adjusting to change. People fear change because they don't like feeling uncomfortable. This year is going to be a year of adjustments and reflection.&nbsp;</p>
<p><img src="http://crazyassbroad.com/media/posts/5/pic11.jpg" alt="" width="1500" height="1071"></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The goal for this broad is going to post at least once a day, everyday, for an entire year. This will give some reflection for the 2018 year and give me, and maybe you, a chance to reflect change. Even if we don't like it, outside influences are constantly changing our perspective and personality. It's how we adjust to those changes that will reflect our character. &nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Preparations for the Holiday Season</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jenn</name>
        </author>
        <link href="http://crazyassbroad.com/preparations-for-christmas.html"/>
        <id>http://crazyassbroad.com/preparations-for-christmas.html</id>

        <updated>2017-12-06T22:53:25-05:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="http://crazyassbroad.com/media/posts/4/IMAG3423_1.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>The holiday festivities are upon us! From finding the perfect gift for our loved one, fightings for parking/the rush at the malls, and the slow&nbsp;internet connections from everyone shopping on Amazon during Cyber Monday; we are really finding the reason for the season.&nbsp;</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>This week everyone is discussing how to act during an office party.</strong></p>
<p>The Office Party: A traditional event prior to Christmas break that is supposed to be festive and cheerful. Did I mention this is an event that involves&nbsp;all of your co-workers? Wait, what?</p>
<p class="align-left">&nbsp;<strong>"What are the Do's and Don't's of attending an office party?" ( Or what I have heard people talk about recently.)&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p><img class="align-center" src="http://crazyassbroad.com/media/posts/4/OfficePartyWestDesMoines.gif" alt="" width="612" height="333"></p>
<p>Step one DON'T GO!!! If you know there is a&nbsp;slight case of acting a foo, you don't have to attend. Drink at home and problem solved!</p>
<p>Step two.. Well, shoot!!! Looks like you still have to go! Okay, you have to go for whatever reason..Stick to one drink. "One drink, you crazy!?" Yes, one drink for every hour you're at the party. You can also alternate water with whatever hard drink is helping you survive your co-workers. Yes, that Scott, Todd, Linda, or Susan will be there and you have to still put on your best fake smile and act like you don't see them everyday! "Yes Susan, I do want another DRINK! THANK YOU!" (I get louder as I get more tipsy. Hmm, maybe this party won't be so bad now... )</p>
<p><img src="http://crazyassbroad.com/media/posts/4/pic2.jpg" alt="" width="630" height="469"></p>
<p>Step 3 TIPSY. Now its time to say your hellos. Make sure the "important people" see that you made face and bounce to the actual party. No party after the office party? Even friggin' better!! I'll get my jam on here!!!&nbsp;</p>
<p><img class="align-center" src="http://crazyassbroad.com/media/posts/4/Snapchat-402429864_1.jpg" alt="" width="411" height="701"></p>
<p>Step 4 Sleepy. The last dwarf you never want to be. But alas, are you there. But first, PIZZA? Of course, there is a late night munchie in your future. Mo pizza, mo fitting that pizza in my mouth!!!&nbsp;</p>
<p>Step 5 Half Sleep. "Beesh, you still got to go to work tomorrow. This party was on a Thursday night." "Grrrreat!"</p>
<p>Step 6 Carefully talk to your co-workers to find out what actually happened at the party. Fill in the blanks for others and make sure there are no embarrassing photos on social media.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<img src="http://crazyassbroad.com/media/posts/4/pic3.jfif" alt="" width="452" height="317"></p>
<p>Step 7 Haha, wait until next year and start all over. Accurate: I think not... right?</p>
<p><img class="align-center" src="http://crazyassbroad.com/media/posts/4/pic5.jpg" alt="" width="640" height="426"></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Introduction</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jenn</name>
        </author>
        <link href="http://crazyassbroad.com/introduction.html"/>
        <id>http://crazyassbroad.com/introduction.html</id>

        <updated>2017-12-03T15:48:04-05:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="http://crazyassbroad.com/media/posts/3/pic2.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>Thank you for coming to my website. I appreciate that you took the time to read something that could be meaningless (yet entertraining) or useful in your everyday lives.</p>
<p>Remember the butterfly effect (Chaos Theory): Something as small as the flutter of a butterfly's wings, can ultimately cause a typhoon halfway across the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This is my attempt to have some sort of positive energy sent out to our virtual world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Enjoy!&nbsp;</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
